SARIT SOPITVETMONTREE

PRODUCT DESIGNER

Yokohama, Kanagawa 070-1262-9500 sarit.sopitvetmontree@gmail.com

PROFILE

Developer-turned-designer with strategy planning and design experience across AI agents, BtoB sales, and healthcare products. Trilingual (Thai/English/Japanese) with firm knowledge in frontend development, enabling effective collaboration with PMs and engineers to ship quality product.

Linkedin https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarit-sopitvetmontree/ Portfolio https://sarit-sopitvetmontree.github.io/Portfolio/

SKILL LANGUAGE

Design Strategy, Competitive research, User persona, User flow IA, Wireframing, UI design, Design system, Responsive design HTML, CSS, Typescript, React, Tailwind, VSCode, Git/Github

Japanese JLPT N2
English TOEIC 960 TOEFL 99
Thai Native

WORK EXPERIENCE

Product Designer

November 2024 - Present

Part-time: July 2024 - Present

Sales Marker - Al SaaS for BtoB business, Tokyo

- Lead the UX and UI design in a multi-designer team for an AI agent application
- Design sales workflow automation feature and run interface QA for a BtoB sales platform
- Maintain and evolve the design system and frontend codebase, ensuring consistency

Lead Product Designer

SIND Inc. - SaaS for Healthcare workers, Tokyo

- Define design strategy as the founding designer for an assistant app for hospital nurses
- Lead end-to-end design, from concept and IA to hi-fi design; achieve 93% user satisfaction
- Establish usage monitoring and analyze feedback to drive continuous improvement

UX Engineer Aug 2023 - October 2024

QunaSys - Quantum computer software development, Tokyo

- Build and iterate on web applications using Next.js, MUI, and related technologies
- Create and refine web application design based on user requests and feedback

Product Designer

Contract : July 2023 - October 2023

Digitech Fabrication - 3D printing service, Bangkok

- Define requirements, create a design system, and deliver hi-fi UI for a 3D printing service
- Collaborate with engineers to ship the website, contributing code as needed

EDUCATION & ACHIEVEMENT

The University of Tokyo 東京大学

April 2022 - March 2024

Master's Degree, Department of Aeronautics and Astronautics

Chulalongkorn University จุฬาลงกรณ์มหาวิทยาลัย

August 2017 - July 2021

Bachelor's Degree, Department of Mechanical Engineering

MEXT Scholarship Awarded the MEXT Scholarship by the Embassy of Japan in Thailand

2021

Olympiad in Informatics Selected to enter the 12th Thailand Olympiad of Informatics

2016